Finding Aid for Clare E. Hoffman Papers 1934-1962
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- General Files 1944-1962, 21.5 linear feet
  - 1961-1962
    - Hoffman House Talks (responses to speeches and requests for copies)
      - Mentally Ill (Box 24)
      - Reuther, Walter (Box 24)
      - Sacrifices (Box 24)
    - Hoffman News Items (Box 24)
    - Hoffman Opinions (Box 24)
    - Hoffman Radio Talks (Box 24)
    - Hoffman Television Appearances (Box 24)
    - Human Events (Box 24)
    - I (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Ideas (Box 25)
    - Invitations (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 25)
    - J (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Johnson, Aben (Box 25)
    - Jordan, Samuel T. (Box 25)
    - K (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Koloseik, Carl (Box 25)
    - L (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - M (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Mc (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - McCurdy, Walter H. (Box 25)
    - McGarity, Rufus P. (Box 25)
    - McKenna, William F. (Box 25)
    - Michigan (Box 25)
    - Miles, Sylvia (Box 25)
    - Miller, Victor (Box 25)
    - Mott, Charles S. (Box 25)
    - N (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Newhouse, Walter (Box 25)
    - News Letters (Box 25)
    - Newspapers
      - In district, 7 folders (Box 25)
      - Out of district (Box 25)
    - Niles Chamber of Commerce (Box 25)
    - O (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - P (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Petro, Sylvester (Box 25)
    - Phair, Walter T. (Box 25)
    - Pomeroy, Paul D. (Box 25)
    - Potts, J. Fred (Box 25)
    - Questionnaires (Box 25)
      (Rarely completed, but with occasional information)
    - R (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Radio Stations, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Rawson, Al (Box 25)
    - Reed, T. John (Box 25)
    - Reuther, Walter (about) (Box 25)
    - S (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Salsbury, Buel (Box 25)
    - Speaking Engagements (Box 25)
    - Stickler, C.L. (Box 25)
    - Sullivan, George E. (Box 25)
    - Supreme Court (Box 25)
    - T (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Television (Box 25)
    - U (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Unemployment (Box 25)
    - Union Now (Box 25)
    - Unions (general) (Box 25)
    - V (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Vander Bunt, Anna (Box 25)
    - Verdonk, John (Box 25)
    - W (miscellaneous) (Box 25)
    - Walker, Edwin A. (Box 25)
    - Whirlpool Corp. (Box 25)
    - White, Jesse (Box 25)
    - Woodward, J.W. (Box 25)
    - York, Bea (Box 25)
- Legislative files 1943-1962, 24.5 linear feet
  Biennial for the period covered, the Legislative Files document Hoffman's work during a specific term of Congress. The files are arranged alphabetically by broad subject heading with sub-divisions where warranted. Consisting mainly of correspondence both with constituents and out-of-district citizens, these files reflect the concerns of Hoffman's correspondents on the issues of the day and the legislation pending before the House. The subjects covered most completely by these files are obviously those areas where Hoffman, because of his interest and committee membership, could claim some expertise. Such subjects include--but are not limited to --Agriculture, Labor, Military, Government Reorganization, and Executive Expenditures. The researcher should note especially files 1947-1948, relating to the legislative history of the Taft-Hartley Act, and the investigations made by a Hoffman-chaired subcommittee of the House Education and Labor Committee investigating strikes in Michigan, Indiana, and Ohio. There is also much material relating to an anti-racketeering subcommittee, 1953-1954, and to the various hearings it held (notably in Kansas City and Minneapolis). The researcher should be alerted to Hoffman's Committee files (boxes 81-88; described elsewhere) which overlap with the files in this Legislative series concerning Hoffman's committee work. Both files should be used for any legislative study.
  - 1943-1944
    - Agriculture
      - General (District) (Box 26)
      - Incentive Payments and AAA (Box 26)
      - Labor in Parity (H.R. 1408) (Box 26)
      - Outside District and Miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Committee Assignment (Box 26)
    - Dies Committee (includes 1942) (Box 26)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 26)
    - Executive Expenditures Committee (Box 26)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (Box 26)
    - Jewish Refugees (Box 26)
    - Labor
      - District General (Box 26)
      - Hobbs bill (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous and Outside District (Box 26)
    - Labor Committee (Box 26)
    - Lend-Lease (Box 26)
    - Lottery (Box 26)
    - Manpower Mobilization (Box 26)
      (S. 607, drafting women, Austin Wadsworth)
    - Military Training (Box 26)
    - Office of Price Administration (Box 26)
    - Peace-Postwar
      - General, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Fulbright Resolution (Box 26)
    - Presidential Term (Box 26)
    - Renegotiation (Box 26)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 26)
    - Salary Limitation (Box 26)
    - Subsidies (Price rollback) (Box 26)
    - Smith Committee (Special Committee to Investigate Executive Agencies) (Box 26)
    - Taxes-Taxation (District) (Box 27)
    - Townsend (District) (Box 27)
    - War (Box 27)
  - 1945-1946
    - Agriculture (Box 27)
    - Anti-Lynching bill (Box 27)
    - Appropriations (Agriculture) (Box 27)
    - Atomic bomb (Box 27)
    - Bretton Woods (Box 27)
    - Conscription (National Service Law) (Box 27)
    - Dies Committee (Box 27)
    - Executive Expenditures Committee (Box 27)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 27)
    - Fair Employment Practices Committee (Box 27)
    - Foreign Policy (Box 27)
    - Full Employment (Box 27)
    - Kenny (Sister) investigation (Box 27)
    - Labor
      - General, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Ball-Burton Hatch Bill (Box 27)
      - Case Bill (Box 27)
      - Truman's Policy (H.R. 4908) (Box 28)
    - Labor Committee (Box 28)
    - Merger (Army/Navy) (Box 28)
    - National Labor Relations Act (Box 28)
    - Office of Price Administration (Box 28)
    - Peace (Box 28)
    - Pearl Harbor (Box 28)
    - Petrillo, James C. (Box 28)
    - Price Control, 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Reorganization, 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 28)
    - Roosevelt Memorial (Box 28)
    - Russia (Box 28)
    - Smith Committee (Box 28)
      (Special Committee to Investigate Executive Agencies)
    - Spain (Box 28)
    - St. Lawrence Waterway (Box 28)
    - Surplus Property (Box 28)
    - Taxes/Taxation (In District) (Box 28)
    - Townsend District (Box 28)
    - Trade Agreements (Box 28)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 28)
    - UNRRA (Box 28)
    - Vivisection (Box 28)
    - Wage Control (Box 28)
    - War Claims Committee (Box 28)
    - War (Box 28)
    - War Department (Box 28)
  - 1947-1948
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 29)
      - Fertilizer Plants (Box 29)
    - Aliens (Box 29)
    - Anti-Lynching (Box 29)
    - Appropriations (agriculture) (Box 29)
    - Communists/Communism (Box 29)
    - Equal Rights (Box 29)
    - Executive Expenditures Committee
      - Miscellaneous (Box 29)
      - Alaska (Box 29)
      - Applications (Box 29)
      - Civil Service Hearings (Box 29)
      - Coast Guard (St. Mary's River) (Box 29)
      - Committee Notices and Miscellaneous Releases (Box 29)
      - Governors' Conference (Chicago) (Box 29)
      - Hoffman, Carl E. (Box 29)
      - Huffman, Hazel (Box 29)
      - Investigations (Suggestion for) (Box 29)
      - Parole of Convicts (Box 29)
      - Reorganization Plans Nos. 1 and 2 (Box 29)
      - Reorganization Plan No. 3 (Box 29)
      - Resolutions (Box 29)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 29)
      - Security Order for Government Agencies (Box 29)
      - Staff Correspondence (Box 29)
      - Subcommittees (Box 29)
      - War Assets Administration (Box 29)
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission (Box 29)
    - Fair Labor Standard Act (Box 29)
    - Federal Employees (disloyalty) (Box 29)
    - Firearms (Box 29)
    - Foreign Policy (Box 29)
    - Hoover Commission (Box 29)
    - Labor
      - General (replied to) (Box 29)
      - General (not replied) (Box 29)
      - Huffman (Hazel) letters (Box 30)
      - Labor Management Relations Act
        - Hartley Bill (H.R. 3020) (Box 30)
        - Amendments (Box 30)
      - Labor-Management Relations, Joint Committee on (Box 30)
      - Meat Strikes (Box 30)
      - Portal-To-Portal (Box 30)
      - Taft-Hartley Act
        - Correspondence (Box 30)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
        - Drafts, etc., 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Unions (Box 30)
    - Labor Committee
      - General (Box 30)
      - Conferences (Box 30)
    - Labor Committee Investigation (non-Michigan)
      - Allis Chalmers (Box 30)
      - Associated Farmers (include photos) (Box 30)
      - Government Services, Inc., 3 folders (Box 30)
      - West Penn Hospital Strike (Pittsburgh) (Box 30)
    - Labor Committee Investigations (Michigan, Indiana, Ohio)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Benton Harbor/St. Joseph
        - General (Box 31)
        - Photos (Box 31)
      - Clinton
        - General (Box 31)
        - Photos (Box 31)
      - Dayton, Ohio
        - General, 3 folders (Box 31)
        - Clippings (Box 31)
        - Exhibits (include photos), 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Dowagiac (include photos) (Box 31)
      - Galion, Ohio
        - General (Box 31)
        - Photos
      - Jackson (Box 31)
      - Kalamazoo, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - Michigan City, Indiana (Box 31)
      - South Haven (include photos) (Box 32)
    - Merger of Army-Navy (Box 32)
    - National Labor Relations Act (Box 32)
    - Petrillo (James) controversy (Box 32)
    - Price Control (Box 32)
    - Reorganization Plans No. 1 (Box 32)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 32)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 32)
    - Socialized Medicine (Box 32)
    - Supreme Court (Box 32)
    - Taxation, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Townsend Plan
      - District (Box 32)
      - Outside District (Box 32)
    - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 32)
    - United Nations (Box 32)
    - Vivisection (Box 32)
    - Wage Control (Box 32)
  - 1949-1950
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 32)
      - Brannan Farm Program (Box 32)
    - Aliens (Box 32)
    - Anti-Lynch Legislation (Box 32)
    - Appropriations (agriculture) (Box 32)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 32)
    - Budget (Box 32)
    - Communism (Box 32)
    - Conservation (Box 32)
    - Displaced Persons Act (Box 32)
    - Education (Box 32)
    - Electoral College (Box 33)
    - Equal Rights (Box 33)
    - Executive Expenditures Committee
      - General (Box 33)
      - Bills (Box 33)
    - Executive Expenditures Subcommittees
      - General (Box 33)
      - Executive Session Hearings (Box 33)
      - Advisory Committees: miscellaneous (Box 33)
      - Institute of Inter-American Affairs (Box 33)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 33)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 33)
      - U.S. Maritime Commission (Box 33)
      - War Housing Disposal Program (Box 33)
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission (Box 33)
    - Federal Security Agency (Box 33)
    - Foreign Policy (Box 33)
    - H-Bomb (Box 33)
    - Highways (Box 33)
    - Hoover Reorganization Plan, 3 folders (Box 33)
    - Hoover Report - Veterans
      - Correspondence (Box 33)
      - Pamphlets, etc (Box 34)
    - Housing (Box 34)
    - Labor (Box 34)
    - Lobby Committee (Box 34)
    - Minimum Wage (Box 34)
    - Mundt-Nixon Bill (Box 34)
    - Price Control (Box 34)
    - Railroads (Box 34)
    - Reorganization Act (Box 34)
    - Reorganization - President's Plan (Box 34)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 5 (Box 34)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 6 (Box 34)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 7 (Box 34)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 18 (Box 34)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 34)
    - Taft-Hartley Act
      - General, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Repeal (Box 34)
      - G. E. questionnaire (Box 34)
    - Taxes
      - Co-Operatives (Box 34)
      - Oleo (Box 34)
    - Townsend Plan (Box 34)
    - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 35)
    - Unification of Armed Services (Box 35)
    - Unions
      - General (Box 35)
      - Robertson Bill (Box 35)
    - Vivisection (Box 35)
    - Wool (Box 35)
  - 1951-1952
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 35)
      - Brannan Plan (Box 35)
    - Aliens (Box 35)
    - Appropriations (agriculture) (Box 35)
    - Budget (Box 35)
    - Conservation (Box 35)
    - Defense Production Act (Box 35)
    - Election Campaigns (Box 35)
    - Equal Rights (Box 35)
    - Executive Expenditures Committee
      - Proposed Investigations (Box 35)
      - General (Box 35)
      - H. Res. 142 (Box 35)
      - H.R. 1545 (Box 35)
      - Soo Inspection (Box 35)
      - W.F. McKenna File (Box 35)
    - Executive Expenditures Subcommittees
      - Bonner Subcommittee (Box 35)
      - Federal Home Loan Bank Board (Box 35)
      - Hardy Subcommittee, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Holifield Subcommittee (Box 35)
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission (Box 35)
    - Fair Trade Practices (Box 35)
    - Farm Labor (Poage Bill) (Box 35)
    - Foreign Policy
      - General (Box 35)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 36)
      - Hoover Speech (Box 36)
      - India (Box 36)
      - Ireland (Box 36)
      - Korea (Box 36)
      - Vatican Envoy (Box 36)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 36)
    - Hoover Commission (Box 36)
    - Impeachment (Box 36)
    - Indians (Box 36)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 36)
      - Taft-Hartley Act (Box 36)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (about) (Box 36)
    - Military (Box 36)
    - Oatis, William N. (reporter arrested by Czechoslovakian government) (Box 36)
    - Obscene Literature (Box 36)
    - Price Controls (selection taken) (Box 36)
    - Primaries (Box 36)
    - Reorganization Plans
      - General (Box 36)
      - No. 1 (Box 36)
      - No. 2 (Box 36)
      - No. 3 (Box 36)
      - No. 4 (Box 36)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 36)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 36)
    - Steel Seizure (Box 36)
    - Tariffs (Box 36)
    - Taxes
      - General (Box 36)
      - Co-operatives (Box 37)
      - Excess Profits (Box 37)
      - Wine (selection taken) (Box 37)
    - Townsend Plan (Box 37)
    - Unions (Box 37)
    - Wage Stabilization Board (Box 37)
    - Wages (Box 37)
  - 1953-1954
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 37)
      - Farm Policy, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Appropriations (Box 37)
    - Armed Services (Box 37)
    - Atomic Energy Committee (Box 37)
    - Budget (Box 37)
    - Coffee (Box 37)
    - Commission of Judicial and Congressional Salaries (Box 37)
    - Communists (Box 37)
    - Constitution, Amendment of (Box 37)
    - Education (Box 37)
    - Education and Labor Committee
      - General (Box 37)
      - Detroit Racketeering (Box 37)
      - Iron Mountain (Box 37)
    - Equal Rights (Box 37)
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission (Box 37)
    - Farm Bureau (Box 37)
    - Federal Pay (Box 37)
    - Foreign Policy
      - General (Box 38)
      - Foreign Aid (Box 38)
      - Indo-China (Box 38)
      - Korea (Box 38)
    - Government Operations Committee
      - General, 4 folders (Box 38)
      - Correspondence (Box 38)
      - Personnel (Box 38)
      - Reports to House Administration Committee (Box 38)
      - Reports from Staff Members (Box 38)
      - Rules and General Information (Box 38)
      - Subcommittees
        - Intergovernmental Relations (Harden), 2 folders (Box 38)
        - International Operations (Brownson) (Box 38)
        - Military Operations (Riehlman) (Box 38)
        - Public Accounts (Bender), 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Special Subcommittees (Box 38)
        - Special Housing Subcommittee (Box 38)
        - Anti-Racketeering
          - General, 2 folders (Box 38)
          - General, 3 folders (Box 39)
          - Political Racketeering (Box 39)
          - Kansas City hearings, 3 folders (Box 39)
          - Minneapolis hearings (Box 39)
          - State Line Dairy, Inc., Niles, Michigan (Box 39)
        - Authority (Box 39)
        - Proposed Investigations
          - General (Box 39)
          - Congressional Junkets (Box 39)
          - Democratic District Conventions (Box 39)
          - Studebaker Corporation (Box 39)
      - Miscellaneous hearings (Box 39)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 39)
    - Indians (Box 39)
    - Korea (Box 39)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 39)
      - Taft-Hartley letters, 1 folders (Box 39)
      - Taft-Hartley letters, 9 folders (Box 40)
    - Lake Levels (Box 40)
    - Obscene Literature (Box 40)
    - Reorganization (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plans (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 1 of 1953 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 2 of 1953 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 6 of 1953 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 8 of 1953 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 9 of 1953 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 10 of 1953 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 1 of 1954 (Box 40)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 2 of 1954 (Box 40)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 40)
    - Taxes (Box 41)
      - General (Box 41)
      - Co-operatives (Box 41)
      - Excess Profits (Box 41)
      - Excise Tax (Box 41)
      - Income (Box 41)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 41)
    - Townsend Plan (Box 41)
    - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 41)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 41)
    - Unions (Box 41)
    - Voting Age (Box 41)
  - 1955-1956
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 41)
      - Farm Policy
        - 1955 (Box 41)
        - 1956 (Box 41)
      - Onion Futures (Box 41)
    - Appropriations (Box 41)
    - Armed Services (Box 41)
    - Bricker Amendment (Box 41)
    - Civil Rights (Box 41)
    - Conservation (Box 41)
    - Constitutional Amendments (Box 41)
    - Education and Labor Committee
      - General (Box 41)
      - Racketeering (Box 41)
    - Equal Rights (Box 41)
    - Farm Bureau (Box 41)
    - Folicy Policy
      - General (Box 41)
      - Formosa (Box 41)
    - Grange (Box 41)
    - Great Lakes Port (Box 41)
    - Highways, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Indians (Box 42)
    - Interior, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 42)
      - Minimum Wage, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Taft-Hartley Act (Box 42)
    - Lake Levels (Box 42)
    - Lake Shore Erosion (Box 42)
    - Narcotics (Box 42)
    - Reorganization (Box 42)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 1 (Box 42)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 2 (Box 42)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 42)
    - Segregation (Box 42)
    - Taxes
      - General (Box 42)
      - Amusement (Box 42)
      - Co-operatives (Box 42)
      - Excise (Box 42)
      - Income (Box 42)
    - Townsend Plan (Box 42)
    - Treaties (Box 42)
    - Unions (Box 42)
    - United Nations (Box 42)
    - Voting Age (Box 42)
    - Water Pollution (Box 42)
    - World Calendar (Box 42)
  - 1957-1958
    - Agricultural
      - General (Box 42)
      - Farm Policy (Box 42)
      - Onion Future (Box 42)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 42)
    - Automobiles (Box 42)
    - Bricker Amendment (Box 42)
    - Civil Rights (Box 42)
    - Communism (Box 42)
    - Conservation (Box 42)
    - Constitutional Amendment (Box 42)
    - Civil Rights (Box 42)
    - Communism (Box 42)
    - Conservation (Box 42)
    - Constitutional Amendment (Box 42)
    - Defense Reorganization (Box 42)
    - Education, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 42)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box 42)
    - Farm Bureau (Box 42)
    - Fluoridation (Box 43)
    - Foreign Aid (Box 43)
    - Foreign Policy
      - General (Box 43)
      - Cuba (Box 43)
      - Hungary (Box 43)
      - Middle East (Box 43)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 43)
    - Grange (Box 43)
    - Great Lakes Ports (Box 43)
    - Immigration (Box 43)
    - Indians
    - Interior Department (Box 43)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 43)
    - Jaycee "Economygrams" (Box 43)
    - Judiciary (Box 43)
    - Labor
      - General (Box 43)
      - S.B. 2888 (Box 43)
      - S.B. 3974 (Box 43)
    - Labor Racketeering (Box 43)
    - Lake Levels (Box 43)
    - Minimum Wage (Box 43)
    - Monopolies (Box 43)
    - Obscene Literature (Box 43)
    - Pollution (Box 43)
    - Religion (Box 43)
    - Reorganization Plan No. 1 of 1958 (Box 43)
    - Rivers and Harbors (Box 43)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 43)
    - School Construction (Box 43)
    - State Rights (Box 43)
    - Supreme Court (Box 43)
    - Taft-Hartley Act (Box 43)
    - Taxes
      - General (Box 44)
      - Co-operatives (Box 44)
      - Excise (Box 44)
      - Income, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Life Insurance Companies (Box 44)
      - Tuition Payments Exemption (Box 44)
    - Television (Box 44)
    - Townsend Plan (Box 44)
    - Unemployment (Box 44)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 44)
    - Unions, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Vivisection (Box 44)
  - 1959-1960
    - Agricultural (Box 44)
      - General (Box 44)
      - Farm Policy (Box 44)
    - Automotive Financing (Box 44)
    - Civil Rights (Box 44)
    - Communism (Box 44)
    - Conservation (Box 44)
    - Cuba (Box 44)
    - Education (Box 44)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 44)
    - Elections (Box 45)
    - Farm Bureau (Box 45)
    - Fluoridation (Box 45)
    - Foreign Aid (Box 45)
    - Foreign Policy (Box 45)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 45)
    - Great Lakes Ports (Box 45)
    - Immigration (Box 45)
    - Indians (Box 45)
    - Interior (Box 45)
    - Labor
      - General (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 45)
      - H.R. 9070 (selection taken), 3 folders (Box 45)
      - Kennedy-Ives Bill (Box 45)
    - Labor Racketeering (Box 45)
    - Lake Levels (Box 45)
    - Loyalty Oath (Box 45)
    - Minimum Wage (Box 46)
    - Monopolies (Box 46)
    - Obscene Literature (Box 46)
    - Pollution (Box 46)
    - School Construction (Box 46)
    - States Rights (Box 46)
    - Taxes
      - General (Box 46)
      - Co-operatives (Box 46)
      - Excise (Box 46)
      - Gasoline (Box 46)
      - Imports (Box 46)
      - Income, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Television (Box 46)
    - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 46)
    - Unemployment (Box 46)
    - Unemployment Compensation (Box 46)
    - Unions (Box 46)
    - Vivisection (Box 46)
  - 1961-1962
    - Agriculture
      - General (Box 47)
      - Farm Policy (Box 47)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 47)
        - Farm Labor (Box 47)
        - Migrant Labor (Box 47)
        - Wheat (Box 47)
    - Animals (Box 47)
    - Anti-Trust (Box 47)
    - Appropriations
      - General (Box 47)
      - Defense (Box 47)
      - State Department (Box 47)
    - Armed Services (Box 47)
    - Automobile Financing (Box 47)
    - China (Box 47)
    - Civil Rights (Box 47)
    - Coal Pipelines (Box 47)
    - Communism (Box 47)
    - Conservation (Box 47)
    - Co-operatives (Box 47)
    - Cuba (Box 47)
    - Disarmament (Box 47)
    - Distressed Areas (Box 47)
    - Education and Labor Committee
      - General (Box 47)
      - Activities of Subcommittees (Box 47)
      - Federal Equal Employment Opportunity Act (Box 47)
      - Minimum Wage (H.R. 3935) (Box 47)
      - NLRB (Pucinski) Subcommittee (Box 47)
      - Training and Retraining of Labor Force (H.R. 7373) (Box 47)
      - Youth Employment Opportunities Act (H.R. 8354) (Box 47)
    - Farm Bureau (Box 47)
    - Federal Aid to Education (selection taken) (Box 47)
    - Federal Aid to Education (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Fluoridation (Box 48)
    - Foreign Aid (Box 48)
    - Foreign Policy
      - General (Box 48)
      - Congo (Box 48)
    - Forestry (Box 48)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 48)
    - Imports (Box 48)
    - Interior (Box 48)
    - Interstate Commerce (Box 48)
    - Labor (Box 48)
    - Loyalty Oath (Box 48)
    - Medicare (selection taken) (Box 48)
    - Mental Health (Box 48)
    - Michigan (Box 48)
    - Minimum Wage (selection taken), 2 folders (Box 48)
    - NLRA-NLRB (Box 48)
    - Picketing (Box 48)
    - Public Power (Box 48)